# Jeferson Arboleda Gómez

Bd James Wyllie 28, Antibes, FR \* (33) 06 49 32 54 50 \* me@jarboleda.me \* https://www.jarboleda.me/

# RÉSUMÉ

August 1992, Colombia. Business analyst living in France since 2017 // 1.5 years of experience as a full stack web developer. After this stage, I went back to university to improve my skills through a Master's degree. Nowadays, I work as a product definition engineer for Amadeus.

## COMPÉTENCES DE BASE

Self-motivated

Detail-oriented

Organized

Determined

# COMPÉTENCES TECHNIQUES

Technical	Python, JavaScript, bash, PHP, SASS, Java
Platforms	IBM Bluemix, Docker, Kubernetes, Google App Engine
Others	Linux (Fedora, Ubuntu), macOS X, Windows

# EXPÉRIENCE PROFESSIONNELLE

#### **AMADEUS/ALTEN**

Product Definition Engineer, Oct 2017 - Now

- Worked in CAR product, being in direct contact with providers (i.e. Avis, Europear) and customers (i.e. Expedia, BCD)
- Implementation of new providers and new functionalities.

## **TCSET**

Lead developer, Jun 2015 - Sep 2016

- Managed the full cycle of several projects, from gathering requirements to maintenance.
- Defined KPIs and objectives for my department.
- Collaborated with my colleagues to assure the delivery on time and quality of our projects.
- Re-engineered company's processes to improve operations such as deployments to production.
- Mentored an intern in day to day operations.

#### **TCSET**

Internship, Feb 2015 - Jun 2015

- Helped in managing the servers of the company (4).
- Helped in managing domains owned by the company (100+) and migrations between providers.

#### EDUCATION

University of Castilla-La Mancha, ES

Degree in Computer Engineering, 2011 - 2015

University of Castilla-La Mancha, ES

Master in Computer Engineering, 2016 - 2017

Cambridge ESOL

Certificate in Advanced English (C1), 2017

#### LANGUAGES

- Spanish (native language)
- English (Advanced C1)

French (Basic - B1)

#### ADDITIONAL DATA

- LinkedIn
- GitHub